But when Nazis took a hold of Germany, the Zionists were the only Jewish group that would collaborate with them while all other Jewish groups boycotted them because Zionists only cared about colonizing Palestine.
Even though Zionism was created by Jewish elite intellectuals and financiers, it was an extremely niche and radical and unwanted movement by most of European Jews.
They completely rejected it. In fact, the first world Zionist organization was supposed to be held in Germany, but the German Jews categorically didn't want it anywhere around them.
So they had to move it to Basel, Switzerland. And when Nazis took hold of Germany, all other Jewish groups inside, outside of Germany recognized Nazism as the bitter enemy of the Jewish people and completely boycotted them, except for Zionists.
And in fact, Theodor Herzl, the father of modern political Zionism, literally wrote in his diary, the anti-Semites will be our most faithful friends. The anti-Semitic countries will be our allies.
And this comes to the famous Ha'ovara agreement between Zionists and Nazis, where, again, every other Jewish group and everyone else was boycotting Germany.
But the Zionists were totally OK to say, hey, don't worry, you just help us move these Jewish people to Palestine and we will make sure to buy manufactured German goods.
And those goods were shipped to Palestine and sold there, benefiting the Nazi regime that was persecuting Jews at a time where everyone else was boycotting them.
This is how callous and disgusting and toxic Zionism is negotiating and colluding with a regime that is genociding your own people.
And this collusion between Zionists and Nazis in order for Zionists to occupy Palestine, the most striking evidence of this was commemorated by this coin that was created in 1934.
And you can have a look what's on one side and what's on the other side.
On one side of the coin, it says a Nazi travels to Palestine and on the other side of the coin, and he tells about it in Der Angriffe, a newspaper.
And this is where Zionists invited Nazis to Palestine to give tours, to show the kibbutzes, to show the settlements.
And so they took this opportunity to team up with colonial powers, with anti-Semitic powers, with fascist powers, because Zionists only cared about colonizing Palestine.
Zionism and anti-Jewishness are both as toxic and evil as they come.
And may the world be free from both one day, and may we see a free Palestine.